{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "Why do they object to ___ here?",
      "a": "smoke",
      "b": "smoking",
      "c": "to smoke",
      "d": "to have smoke",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n\n- Object to + V_ing",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "We aren't accustomed to ___ up so early.",
      "a": "get",
      "b": "have got",
      "c": "getting",
      "d": "having got",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Accustomed to + V_ing \n- The tense of this sentence is simple present so the answer \"having got\" is not correct",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Watching a fine player is a good way of ___ one's own game.",
      "a": "to improve",
      "b": "being improved",
      "c": "improving",
      "d": "to be improved",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Preposition ( by, on, of...) + V_ing \n- A good way of + V_ing \n- This is active voice, so the answer \"being improved\" is not correct",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I am certainly looking forward to ___ the champion.",
      "a": "watching",
      "b": "watch",
      "c": "be watched",
      "d": "being watched",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n\n- Looking forward to + V_ing\n\n- This sentence is active voice: the anwer \"being watched\" is not correct",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "There is one more book worth ___.",
      "a": "read",
      "b": "of reading",
      "c": "to reading",
      "d": "reading",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n\n- Worth + V_ing\n\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I remember ___ the maid ___ out of the office yesterday.",
      "a": "to keep, to wait",
      "b": "keeping, to wait",
      "c": "keeping, waiting",
      "d": "keeping, wait",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n\n- Remember + Verb_ing: Remember something  that have already done\n\n- Rememer + To Verb: Remeber to do somethinbg\n\n- Keep + Verb_ing: Let the action happen in long time",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What do you say ___ on a hike?",
      "a": "to going",
      "b": "to go",
      "c": "about going",
      "d": "going",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n\n- Structure: What do you say to V_ing?",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "He could not help ___ his lot.",
      "a": "satisfying with",
      "b": "satisfy at",
      "c": "being satisfied with",
      "d": "be satisfied at",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n\n- Can not help + V_ing: not able to refrain from doing something; not able not to do something\n\n- Be satisfied with: somebody feel pleased with something\n\n- Satisfy: Try to meet somebody's expectation",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Every morning he spends two hours ___ papers and magazines.",
      "a": "for reading",
      "b": "on reading",
      "c": "reading",
      "d": "to read",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n\n-Spend + time/money + Ving\n\nE.g: I spend all my free time reading.\n\n- Spend + time/money + On + Something\n\nE.g: I spend all my money on books.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "He is not capable ___ such difficult work in a day.",
      "a": "to finish",
      "b": "to have finished",
      "c": "for finishing",
      "d": "of finishing",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n\n- Capable of + V_ing: having the strength or ability to do sth",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}